let's talk about your daily routine can
you tell me about your daily routine
when I first get up I don't like doing
anything um high maintenance or too
quick I like to take my time um once I
wake up I like to just be on my phone
and then gradually get on from there get
up and do my skin care I start getting
dressed and then go downstairs I make
some coffee or tea even matcha I love
much so yeah that's kind of my morning
routine has your routine changed since
you were a child so growing up I didn't
really have a routine because when
you're a child you just do whatever but
growing up I came to realize that it's
important to have like a set um routine
on what to do and how to take care of
yourself how to maintain a better
routine throughout the day so yeah my
routine has drastically changed
throughout um my life is there anything
you would like to add to your daily
routine I would like to incorporate uh
more of like meditation to just be able
to ground myself um when needed I
haven't been able to do that as of
recently but I would like to incorporate
that in my routine because I think it's
important to just be able to um um have
that minute to yourself and just feel
grounded let's talk about flowers have
you ever received flowers as a gift yes
I have um actually recently I did
receive flowers and I can't talk enough
about flowers I love everything about
them like the variations that you find
the different types and colors as simple
as like roses to let's say tulips I love
everything about them on what special
occasions do people give Flowers in Your
Country uh from where I'm from they
usually use flowers for say birthdays or
uh
weddings and flowers are just uh common
to receive especially here with my
friends we usually like gift each other
flowers for each other's birthdays or
even just like a normal like a thank you
like just to show appreciation to a
person what kind of flowers would you
like to receive as a present so I've
never received uh sunflowers and when I
was a kid I just looking at sunflowers I
was always amazed by how they look and I
would want to like touch one because
I've never like seen how it looks like
in real life I've only seen it through
pictures so I would like to receive um
sunflowers now let's talk about food do
you enjoy cooking I don't personally
cook for myself just because I wasn't
really
into um cooking I do however like baking
I like to bake desserts I like to make
um let's say cake uh chocolate cake or
cookies whenever I feel bored at home
and there's literally nothing to do I
find myself grabbing the ingredients in
the cupboards or just baking it's really
fun and just the hard work that I put
into it versus the aftermath I feel like
it's worth it do you think that you have
a healthy diet personally I don't think
that I have a healthy diet I usually eat
whatever is available I try to be
mindful of what I put into my body
especially because how I see people um
develop some issues use with uh the food
that they take and especially because as
I'm growing older my metabolism is going
to be different so I try to be aware but
usually my diet isn't that great how
often do you order food online I usually
order I would say about two to three
times a week um other than that I would
just eat at home I would actually very
much prefer um homemade food rather than
ordering online when there's nothing to
eat at home I tend to gravitate towards
uh ordering through the app um fast food
now let's talk about movies what are the
advantages of seeing a movie in the
cinema I would say the advantages of
seeing a movie in a cinema would be that
you get to watch it as soon as it comes
out you get to watch it in a bigger
screen instead of just staying at home
and watching it through your laptop or a
TV I don't think there's a lot of
advantages in my opinion but I really
like the The Experience uh let's say if
you're watching it in terms of like um
uh IM through IMAX that experience is
really nice um because of how the sound
system is it's it's a really nice
experience uh do you like watching
movies alone or with other people so
when it's like a like an indie film I
like to watch it alone because I feel
like that's not everyone's cup of tea
but with psychological thrillers or
horror movies especially I love watching
it with other people because I cannot
stand watching it alone I get really
scared when it's horror films so having
a company with you it's it's much better
so last year my mom who usually prepares
the meals at home she uh was away for
vacation so I was in charge of uh
cooking the food at home I learned to
prepare this Meal which was pasta
arabiata it's very simple to some people
but from um perspective where I've never
really cooked anything at home it was
like a big step for me I learned this uh
recipe online like I just skimmed
through random website and um I started
following the recipe and I actually had
a bit of help from my cousin um I the
reason why I chose this um food to
prepare um was because my dad really
enjoys pasta Arata he wouldn't eat any
other type of pasta except that for some
reason it doesn't have any like uh meat
it's just literally pasta and sauce and
it was pretty quick like when I started
uh preparing it uh it didn't take me
that long which I liked because I hate
spending hours in the kitchen just
waiting to cook I mean to eat something
I think that takes the fun out of
cooking cuz I just want it quick the
part that I liked about uh the meal that
I prepared was uh that it was quick but
also at the same time it was uh it was
very delicious like I added um organic
uh tomato I used not like the canned um
uh sauce I made it from scratch so
that's what I enjoyed about it so we've
been talking about food and we're going
to continue to talk about cooking and
working in the food industry do you
think it's important for children to
learn how to
cook to thank you for watching this
video I want to give you a free course
that has helped thousands of students
improve their ey out speaking score what
it's going to do is take you through
every single part of the test and give
you strategies for part one part two and
part three and also allow you to
practice at home for free and get
feedback to sign up for that for free
all you have to do is just click the
link in the description thanks very much
and let's get back to the video so I
love the idea where kids grow up in a
household where they learn how to cook
personally I've never I I was never
taught how to cook properly just to
prepare like random dishes small dishes
like oh putting the the cheese on the
plate because in um Arab Cuisines you
will find like these tiny dishes spread
out like uh called mza so it's just like
tiny appetizers and that's how I learned
to prepare uh The Breakfast Table but um
I would personally teach my kids how to
cook if I learned to it's myself because
I feel like learning that from a young
age could benefit uh further uh future
do you think that high school children
should learn to cook at home or at
school I never heard anyone cooking at
school honestly but um I think at home
would be much preferable because you
have everything there the ingredients is
already in the kitchen and especially
because let's say a parent could help
guide you on what to use what not to use
what to stay away from and what goes
with what so you can test out what is
suitable for your liking now let's talk
about working as a chef do you think it
would be enjoyable to work as a
professional chef from my knowledge I've
only seen professional chefs um let's
say in cooking shows or in um Hell's
Kitchen so I think it's very um a very
tiring job especially because if you
have like let's say 20 people coming in
at the same time ordering different
meals it's going to be a very tough job
or um tough on you to be a professional
chef trying to keep up with different um
meals what if you mess up like you never
know um so yeah it's I don't I think
it's an easy job how much influence do
celebrity chefs have on what Ordinary
People cook to thank you for making it
this far in the video I want to give you
10% off our VIP course I VIP course is
the most successful ILS course in the
world that is a fact because we have
more band seven eight and nine success
stories than any other I course in the
entire world we do that by simplifying
the whole I process supporting you with
some of the best teachers in the world
and being with you every step of the way
until you get the score that you need
all you have to do is just look down in
the description just click that and you
can sign up if you have any questions
about the VIP course always feel free to
get in touch with us we answer 100% of
the questions that we get hope that you
become a VIP if not enjoy the rest of
this free video so the influence uh that
celebrities celebrity chefs have on
ordinary people I believe is uh great
because of how how they add their
personal touch into a dish Gordon Ramsey
I know that he is known for his filet
minion I think um and the way he
prepares it he wants it to be perfect
and I think that like not everyone can
achieve that at home but learning
through what he does can um can make
them very intrigued to make this dish
that's the end of the speaking test well
done thank you so much